Benjamin Vaughan Papers 1746-1900 Mss.B.V46p
American Philosophical Society
- Series II. General Correspondence, 1746-1952; 6.5 linear feet (Box 2-27)
  - ALS to Abbott, Jacob, 1803-1879, 1836 August 15; 1 p.; McKeen, John
  - ALS to Abbott, Jacob, 1803-1879, 1838 June 5; 1 p.; Abbot, Abiel, 1770-1828
  - ALS to Merrick, Mary, 1838 July 17; 6 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Merrick, John, 1766-1861, 1839 January 22; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Merrick, Mary, 1840 February 6; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Merrick, John, 1766-1861, 1840 June 11; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - AMs, extract from "Souvenirs d'un diplomate", 1840 September 26-28; 3 p.; M. de Bacourt
  - AMsS, Vaughan Club material, 1841 January 15; 2 p.; Hollinshead, Benjamin M
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah, 1841 September 29; 3 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - ALS to Lucy and Martha Emmons, 1841 December 23; 4 p.; Emmons, L
  - ALS to Sweetzer, Seth, 1842 March 19; 4 p.; Merrick, John, 1766-1861
  - ALS to Abbott, Jacob, 1803-1879, 1843 May 1, 2, 5, 7, 10; 4 p.; Abbott, Harriett Vaughan
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah, 1843 June 3; 2 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - ALS to Bulfinch, Thomas, 1843 October 18; 1 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
    Porchased originally with Abbott-Vaughan. Genealogy. Oct. 1953.
  - ALS to Bulfinch, Thomas, 1843 October 3; 1 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
    Porchased originally with Abbott-Vaughan. Genealogy. Oct. 1953. Housed with previous letter.
  - ALS to Merrick, John, 1766-1861, 1843 November 18; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Merrick, John, 1766-1861, 1844 September 18; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Merrick, John, 1766-1861, 1844 October 1; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah, 1844 October 2; 4 p.; Aspinwell, E. P
  - ALS to Merrick, John, 1766-1861, 1844 October 2; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Merrick, John, 1766-1861, 1844 September 30; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ADS, Invoice of plate shipped to John Merrick for Mrs. Rebecca Merrrick, [1844 October]; 4 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Caroline, 1845 March 6; 3 p.; Vaughan, William Manning
  - ALS to Merrick, John, 1766-1861, 1845 May 1; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah, 1845 May 19; 3 p.; Grant, William S
  - ALS to Merrick, John, 1766-1861, 1845 June 30; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Merrick, John, 1766-1861, 1845 July 21; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah, 1845 August 4; 1 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah, 1845 October 18; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Merrick, John, 1766-1861, 1849 June 12; 1 p.; Merrick, T. B
  - ALS to Merrick, John, 1766-1861, 1849 August 3; 1 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - ALS to Merrick, John, 1766-1861, 1844 October 1; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, J. A, 1850 November 21; 3 p.; Merrick, John, 1766-1861
  - ALS to Snider, Jacob, 1851 February 17; 1 p.; Sparks, Jared, 1789-1866
  - ALS to Snider, Jacob, 1851 March 5; 1 p.; Sparks, Jared, 1789-1866
  - ALS to Vaughan, J. A, 1851 April 11; 4 p.; Merrick, John, 1766-1861
  - ALS to Merrick, George, 1851 June 4; 2 p.; Merrick, John, 1766-1861
  - ALS to Merrick, George, 1851 July 23; 3 p.; Merrick, John, 1766-1861
  - ALS to [?], 1852 November 17, 23; 4 p.; Merrick, John, 1766-1861
  - ALS to [Abbott], Edward, 1852 December 18; 3 p.; Abbott, Jacob, 1803-1879
  - ALS to [Merrick], John and Harriet, 1856 August 28; 3 p.; Merrick, John, 1766-1861
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Manning, 1858 March 5; 3 p.; Riley, Theodore W., Jr
  - AMsS, Hymn, 1858 June 2; 1 p.; Merrick, John, 1766-1861
  - AMsS, Ordination hymn for Edward [Abbott], 1863 July 28; 2 p.
  - AMsS, A Sermon, 1866; 4 p.; Hall, C. H
  - Pencil sketch of E. T. P., 1872 March 13; 1 item; L., H.
    Rough pencil sketch of woman reading, made in Paris.
  - ALS to [Parkman], Mary, [1872] March 30; 4 p.; Lee, Henry, Jr
  - ALS to [Parkman], Mary, [1872] May 20; 4 p.; Lee, Henry, Jr
  - Als to [Vaughan], Ellen, [1872] October 14; 4 p.; Lee, Henry, Jr
  - Als to [Vaughan], Ellen, 1872 December 14; 1 p.; Twisleton, Edward
  - ALS to Kidder, Vaughan & Co, 1873 February 24; 1 p.; Harvard University Observatory
  - ALS to Mary, 1873 February 25; 1 p.; Vaughan, B
  - ANS, Announcement of the marriage of Katharine Kelley Duhning to Edward Abbott, 1883 August 21; 1 p.
  - ALS to Vaughan, William W, 1885 March 19; 5 p.; Jay, John
  - ALS to Vaughan, Martha Agry, 1886 May 4; 4 p.; Vaughan, William W
  - ALS to Vaughan, Martha Agry, 1886 May 7; 4 p.; Vaughan, William W
  - ALS to Vaughan, Martha Agry, 1886 May 8; 4 p.; Vaughan, William W
  - ALS to Vaughan, Martha Agry, 1886 May 12; 7 p.; Vaughan, William W
  - ALS to Vaughan, Martha Agry, 1886 May 13; 4 p.; Vaughan, William W
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Warren, 1886 May 20; 2 p.; Viscount Evelyn
  - AN, copies from the church register at Caermathen of Vaughan Family genealogical notes, 1886 May 27; 2 p.; Cambridge Social Union
  - ALS to [Vaughan, William Warren], 1886 May 27; 6 p.; Viscount Evelyn
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Warren, 1886 June 24; 4 p.; Lloyd-Vaughan, W. P. H
  - ALS to Vaughan, W. M, 1888 August 31; 1 p.; Vaughan, William Warren
  - ALS to Vaughan, W. M, 1889 July 26; 4 p.; Vaughan, William Warren
  - ALS to Vaughan, W. M, 1889 July 27; 4 p.; Vaughan, William Warren
  - TL to Fraley, Frederick, 1892 July 25; 3 p.; Hart, Charles Henry
  - ALS to Loring, Charles G, 1892 July 25; 1 p.; Hart, Charles Henry
    Includes copies.
  - TD, A list of Benjamin Vaughan-Sir Joseph Banks correspondence purchased by B. Vaughan, 1894 February; 5 p.
  - AD, Meteorological observations, 1894-1935; 1 p.
  - AL to Dr. Abbott, 1897 November 1; 1 p.; Abbott, Charles
  - ALS to Otis, Elizabeth G, 1902 August 8; 3 p.; Emmons, Lucy M
  - AN to Vaughan, B, 1908; 1 p.
  - TLS to Mrs. W. W. Vaughan, 1920 April 20; 2 p.; Farr, Daniel H
  - TN, Valentine sent to Vaughan, William Warren, [1922 Febraury 12]; 1 p.
  - TLS to Mrs. William Warren Vaughan, 1922 August 9; 1 p.; London University College Hospital.
  - ALS to Vaughan, W. W, 1926 September 24; 3 p.; Vaughan, G. H. Lloyd
  - TLS to Mrs. W. W. Vaughan, 1928 January 16; 5 p.; Murray, John
  - Als to Mrs. Barrett Wendell, [1928 August]; 1 p.; Mary
  - TLS to Mrs. W. W. Vaughan, 1929 March 26; 3 p.; Murray, John
  - ALS to Mrs. W. W. Vaughan, 1929 July 1; 2 p.; Lord Lansdowne
  - ALS to Mrs. W. W. Vaughan, 1929 July 11; 2 p.; Leigh, Agnes
  - ALS to Lord Landsdowne, [1929 September 13]; 4 p.; Vaughan, Ellen
  - Als to Mrs. W. W. Vaughan, 1929 September 30; 2 p.; Lord Lansdowne
  - Als to Mrs. W. W. Vaughan, [1930 January 1]; 2 p.; Leigh, Agnes
  - ALS to [Vaughan] Samuel, 1930 April 12; 2 p.; Bacon, Marie L
  - ALS to Mrs. W. W. Vaughan, [1930] November 23; 2 p.; Prince, Helen Choate
  - TLS to Mrs. W. W. Vaughan, 1931 February 3; 2 p.; Maine Historical Society Library.
  - TLS to Mrs. W. W. Vaughan, 1931 February 4; 1 p.; Davis, Walter G
  - TLS to Mrs. W. W. Vaughan, 1931 February 9; 1 p.; Davis, Walter G
  - TLS to Vaughan, Samuel, 1931 May 2; 1 p.; Pierson, George Wilson
  - TLS to Vaughan, William Warren, 1931 May 23; 6 p.; Gould, Alicia Bache
  - TLS to Vaughan, William Warren, 1931 July 1; 2 p.; Gould, Alicia Bache
  - TLS to Vaughan, William Warren, 1931 July 5; 2 p.; Gould, Alicia Bache
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Warren, 1931 August 1; 1 p.; Merrick, J. Vaughan
  - TLS to Mrs. Marvin, 1931 December 31; 6 p.; [Madeira], Edward W
  - ALS to Mrs. W. W. Vaughan, [1933] July 4; 1 p.; Fayerweather, M. D
  - TLS to Mrs. W. W. Vaughan, 1933 July 7; 2 p.; Peabody, Francis G
  - ALS to Mrs. W. W. Vaughan, 1933 July 19; 4 p.; Laura
  - ALS to Mrs. W. W. Vaughan, 1933 July 20; 1 p.; Laura
  - ALS to Mrs. G. Lane, [1933 July 27]; Curtis, Anita
  - ALS to Mrs. W. W. Vaughan, 1933 August 21; 3 p.; L. E. R
  - ALS to Mrs. W. W. Vaughan, [1933 September 18]; 1 p.; Louisa
  - ALS to Mrs. W. W. Vaughan, [1933] September 21; 1 p.; Crosby, Henrietta
  - ALS to Mrs. W. W. Vaughan, 1933 November 24; 2 p.; Shepard, Katherine
  - TLs to [Vaughan] Ellen, 1934 February 13; 2 p.; Morison, Samuel Eliot
  - TN to Vaughan, William, 1936 August 3; 1 p.; Langdon Parker Marvin, Mr.; Langdon Parker Marvin, Mrs.
  - ALS to Mrs. Fordyce Coburn, 1938 December 22; 3 p.; Mayo, Lawrence S
  - TLS to Mrs. Langdon Marvin, 1941 March 19; 1 p.; Ferrand, Max
  - TLS to Mrs. Langdon Marvin, 1941 March 22; 1 p.; Farrand, Beatrix
  - TLS to Mrs. Langdon Marvin, 1941 April 23; 1 p.; Hamer, P. M
  - TLS to Mrs. Langdon Marvin, 1941 June 30; 1 p.; Farrand, Beatrix
  - TLS to Mrs. Langdon Marvin, 1941 September 15; 7 p.; Farrand, Max
  - ALS to [Mrs. Marvin], 1946 May 20; 5 p.; Madeira, Edward W
  - Benjamin Vaughan papers purchased from Goodspeed. Table of contents
  - TLS Cy to Lansdowne, William Petty, Marquis of, 1737-1805, 1782 July 9; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - TLS Cy to Lansdowne, William Petty, Marquis of, 1737-1805, 1782 August 21; 1 p.; George III, King of Great Britain, 1738-1820
  - ALS to Vaughan, John, 1756-1841, 1783 February 15; 2 p.; Jay, John, 1745- 1829
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 January 14; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 July 18; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 April 18; 3 p; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1802 August 23; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1803 January 31; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1803 February 14; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - AL, unidentified, n.d.; 4 p.
  - AL, unidentified, n.d. [29 January]; 4 p.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 1 p.; Adams, John Quincy, 1767-1848
  - Invitation to the marriage of Austin Abbott and Anna Worth, n.d. [24 September]; 1 p.
  - Sketch of the tombstone of Gorham D. Abbot, n.d.; 1 p.
  - Invitation to the marriage of Phillips Abbott and Jennie L. Beardsley, n.d. [20 December]; 1 p.
  - ALS to Bly, n.d.; 5 p.; W. J. B
  - AMscy, extracts of his writings, n.d.; 12 p.; Bacon, Francis
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Sarah Manning], n.d; 2 p.; Collins, John, Jr.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d; 2 p.; Crawford, Adair, 1748-1795
  - AL to Gardiner, Emma, n.d; 4 p.; Emmons, Lucy Vaughan
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, n.d; 2 p.; Emmons, Lucy Vaughan
  - AL to Gardiner, Emma, n.d; 4 p.; Emmons, Lucy Vaughan
  - AL to Gardiner, Emma, n.d; 4 p.; Emmons, Lucy Vaughan
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, n.d. [26 December]; 4 p.; Emmons, Lucy Vaughan
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, n.d. [15 November]; 4 p.; Emmons, Lucy Vaughan
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, n.d. [5 April]; 4 p.; Emmons, Lucy Vaughan
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, n.d. [1 April]; 4 p.; Emmons, Lucy Vaughan
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, n.d. [6 March]; 4 p.; Emmons, Lucy Vaughan
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, n.d. [5 January]; 4 p.; Emmons, Lucy Vaughan
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, n.d. [22 January]; 3 p.; Emmons, Lucy Vaughan
  - AL to Emmons, William, n.d.; 4 p.
  - AMs, concerning fire engines, n.d.; 2 p.
  - AMsS, concerning the establishment of a public loan office in Great Britain, n.d.; 18 p.; Forster, Johann Reinhold, 1729-1798
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], n.d.; 2 p.; Gardiner, Robert Hallowell, 1782-1864
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, n.d.; 4 p.; Grant, Elizabeth F. Vaughan
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d. [8 May]; 4 p.; Grant, Elizabeth F. Vaughan
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, n.d. [7 May]; 4 p.; Grant, Elizabeth F. Vaughan
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 2 p.; Gregoire
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], n.d. [30 October]; 1 p.; Griffin, Bristo
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, n.d.; 1 p.; [Hackney, R. V]
  - ALS to [?], n.d.; 4 p.; Hassan, Abal
  - ALS to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, n.d. [7 May]; 2 p.; Hawkins, J[ohn]
  - ALS to Dr. Bridgham, n.d.; 1 p.; Herrick, Israel
  - ALS to Newcombe, R. E, n.d.; 2 p.; Hoyt, E
  - Announcement of the marriage of Oliver Johnson to Jenny M. Abbott, n.d. [27 August]; 1 p.
    Purchased originally with Abbott-Vaughan. Genealogy, Oct. 1953.
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], n.d. [July]; 1 p.; Lansdowne, William Petty, Marquis of, 1737-1805
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, n.d.; 4 p.; Lansdowne, William Petty, Marquis of, 1737-1805
  - ALS to Parkman, Mary, n.d. [13 July]; 4 p.; Lee, E. V
  - ALS to Reeder, John, n.d.; 2 p.; Lee, William
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 1 p.; La Favre, Nicholas
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d. [11 October]; 1 p.; Thomas Lewis & Son
  - ANS to Vaughan, W. W, n.d. [25 December]; 1 p.; Marvin, Diana Vaughan
  - Genealogy of McMaster family, n.d.; 1 p.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, n.d.; 2 p.; Merrick, Rebecca Vaughan
  - AL to Merrick, Rebecca Vaughan, n.d.; 6 p.
  - ALS to Vaughan, J. A, n.d. [24 November]; 4 p.; Merrick, Rebecca Vaughan
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, n.d. [1 August]; 3 p.; Merrick, Rebecca Vaughan
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 1 p.; Neave, Thomas
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 1 p.; Page, Benjamin, Jr
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, n.d.; 3 p.; Pennefather, Samuel
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d. [7 March]; 1 p.; Pinckney, Thomas, 1750-1828
  - Poem, by Viau, Theophile de, 1590-1626, n.d.; 2 p.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 1 p.; Price, Richard, 1723-1791
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 1 p.; Price, Richard, 1723-1791
  - AMs, Account of the last illness of Joseph Priestley, n.d.; 8 p.; [Priestly, Joseph, Jr]
  - ALS to Merrick, Rebecca Vaughan, n.d. [10 November]; 3 p.; Priestley, Mary Wilkinson
  - Concerning Richards, Henry and Francis, n.d.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 3 p.; Riddell, W
  - ALS to Merrick, Rebecca Vaughan, n.d. [22 August]; 3 p.; Russell, M
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], n.d. [23 July]; 2 p.; Shipley, Anna Maria
  - Address sheet to Benjamin Vaughan, n.d.; 1 p.; [Snow, Gideon]
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d. [26 July]; 3 p.; Spooner, Charles
  - AMsS, concerning the Americans, n.d.; 2 p.; Stael, (Anne-Louise-Germaine), Madame de, 1766-1817
  - ALS Cy to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d. [27 November]; 1 p.; Stewart, Dugald, 1753-1828
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, n.d.; 3 p.; Vaughan, Barbara
  - AMs, concerning Locke on religion, n.d.; 27 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AMs, An account of a new mwthod of preserving water good at see, as well as restoring it when putrid; extracted by Claude Louis Berthollet with remarks by Benjamin Vaughan, n.d.; 6 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AMs, account of a wooden bridge, n.d.; 6 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AMs, extracts from the memoirs of Peter Henry Bruce, n.d.; 11 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AMs, Observations in Fort William and betewwn Madra and Calcutta. Made by Col. Thomas D. Pearse commandants of the artillary and second in command of the Bagal Army, 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AMs, Translation of a paper in the Memoirs of the French Royal Academy of Sciences, on the subject "A Property of the number 9", n.d.; 9 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AMs, An account of a regiment of light infantry using snow-shoes in Norway, n.d.; 7 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AMs, A machine for using water by H. Sargent of Whitehavon, n.d.; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - Sketch of apparatus for impregnating fluids with factitious air, n.d.; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AMs, Description of a still, n.d.; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - Recollections of Benjamin and Sarah Manning Vaughan, 39 p.; [Everett, E]
  - Memorandum concerning events which Benjamin Vaughan was too busy to study, 1 p.
  - concerning Benjamin Vaughan, n.d.; 3 p.
  - concerning Benjamin Vaughan's Estate, n.d.; 1 p.
  - ALS to [?], n.d.; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to [?], n.d.; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to [?], n.d.; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to [?], n.d.; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to [?], n.d.; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to [?], n.d.; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to [?], n.d.; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to [?], n.d.; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to [Aikin, John, 1747-1822], n.d. [November]; 8 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Mr. Cheever, n.d.; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALStcy to Franklin, Benjamin, 1706-1790, n.d.; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to [Jay, John, 1745-1829], n.d.; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to [Henry Petty-Fitzmaurice, third marquis of lansdowne], n.d.; 39 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to [Lansdowne, William Petty, Marquis of, 1737-1805], n.d.; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Lansdowne, William Petty, Marquis of, 1737-1805, n.d.; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to [Lansdowne, William Petty, Marquis of, 1737-1805], n.d.; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to [Lansdowne, William Petty, Marquis of, 1737-1805], n.d.; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Dr. Page, Jr, n.d.; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to Mrs. Pinckney, n.d.; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to Vaughan, John, 1756-1841, n.d.; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to Vaughan, John, 1756-1841, n.d.; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854, n.d.; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-1827, n.d.; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, n.d.; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, n.d.; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to Wilkinson, John, n.d.; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to Wilson, James, n.d.; 11 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 1 p.
  - AL to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d. [February 14]; 4 p.
  - AL to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], n.d.; 1 p.
  - AL to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 1 p.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - AL to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, n.d.; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to [?], n.d.; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d. [March 22]; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d. [March 6]; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d. [February 11]; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], n.d.; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - List of conveyances, n.d.; 11 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - Sale of assets of Samuel Vaughan, Jr., to William Vaughan in part payment of debt, n.d.; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - Epitaph on tomb of Charles Vaughan, n.d.; 1 p.
  - ALS to Lord Lansdowne, n.d.; 4 p.; Vaughan, Ellen
  - ALS to Lord Lansdowne, n.d.; 3 p.; Vaughan, Ellen
  - ALS to Merrick, Rebecca Vaughan, n.d.; 4 p.; Vaughan, Harriet Manning
  - AL to Vaughan, Harriet Manning, n.d.; 4 p.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d. [27 September]; 3 p.; Vaughan, Henry
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], n.d. [17 December]; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d. [3 August]; 2 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - AL to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 3 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - Miscellaneous notes concerning the quandrant, 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - List of creditors of John Vaughan, n.d.; 1 p.
  - Samuel Vaughan estate. Division of Hallowell lands, 1 p.
  - AL to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 2 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-1827
  - Instructions to Samuel Vaughan regarding deeds, n.d.; 1 p.
  - ALS to [?], n.d. [26 November]; 1 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, n.d. [16 February]; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, n.d. [4 April]; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, n.d. [30 May]; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, n.d. [30 June]; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, n.d. [11 July]; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, n.d. [16, 19 November]]; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, n.d. [16 October]; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, n.d.; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, n.d.; 6 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Gardiner, Robert Hallowell, 1782-1864, n.d. [5 March]; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Merrick, Rebecca Vaughan, n.d.; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Mrs. Ridley, n.d.; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d. [1 March]; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d. [ March]; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d. [28 August]; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - AL to Vaughan, Harriet, n.d.; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Shaw, W. S, n.d.; 1 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Manning
  - ALcy to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 2 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Manning
  - ALS to Vaughan, Harriet, n.d.; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Manning
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, n.d. [14 May]; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Manning
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, n.d.; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ADS, bill against William and Mary Bell, 1 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - Tickets of admission, n.d. [24 January]; 1 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - ALS to Vaughan, Harriet, n.d.; 4 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - ALS to Vaughan, Harriet, n.d.; 4 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, n.d.; 2 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
    In french
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, n.d.; 4 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, n.d. [20 May]; 1 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - AMsStcy, speech on civil service reform, n.d.; 33 p.; Vaughan, William W
  - ALS to Livermore, D. P, n.d.; 4 p.; Vaughan, William W
  - AL to Vaughan, William W, n.d.; 4 p.
  - Vaughan family Bible, n.d.; 1 p.
  - Vaughan family genealogy, n.d.; 81 p.
  - Vaughan family genealogy, n.d.; 8 p.
  - TMs, The Vaughan Family and Hallowell, 8 p.
  - Warren family genealogy, n.d.; 6 p.
  - Warren family genealogy, n.d.; 3 p.
  - Description of the weather-cock mill, n.d.; 3 p.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 1 p.; Webber, Joseph
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d.; 3 p.; Whitover, Benjamin
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, n.d. [27 February]; 1 p.; Willett, [Marinus]
  - ALS to Oliver, Thomas, n.d.; 3 p.; Wise, P
- Series III. Manuscripts, ca.1780-1812; 0.75 linear feet (Box 28-30)